New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, Environmental Conservation Division (PEF/ENCON); Records apap114
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Files, 1978-2000; 1; 7.2 cubic ft.
  - United Field Representatives and Staff Union / United Steel Workers of America, Negotiations, 1983; 1986-1989; 1995; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 53)
  - United University Professions, 1983; 1985-1986; 1998 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 54)
  - Use of Union Credit Card Investigation, Report, 1984 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 55)
  - Veterans' Issues, 1983-1993; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 56)
  - Voluntary Reduction in Work Schedule, 1983-1985; 1988; 1991 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 57)
  - Workers' Compensation, Policies and Manuals, 1985-1988; 1993 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 58)
  - Workers' Compensation Reform, Position Paper, 1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 59)
  - Agency Work Force Management Plan and Transfer Card, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Cash Receipts Journal Register, 1981-1982 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Civil Service Employees Association, Contracts, 1995; 1988; 1991; 1999 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1984-1985; 1988; 1991-1993; 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Coors Beer Boycott, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Corporate Credit Cards, 1988; Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Divisions Constitution, Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Election Rules, Petitions, Candidates, Campaigns, 1982; 1985; 1993 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Improper Practice Cases, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Joseph Scacalossi Scholarship, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Keenan, Mike, Contract Grievance Forms, 1989; Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - New York State Advisory Commission Executive Order, Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - New York State PEF, Organizational Chart, Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Professional, Scientific, and Technical Unit, Election, 1978 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Promotion Tests, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Reduction in Force Impact Form, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Retirement Incentive Program, 1991; 1995; 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Retirement Plan Court Case, 1983-1984 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Roll Call Quorum Vote, 1980 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Solidarity Committee of the Capital District, 1984-1985; 1988; Undated (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - United Public Service Employees Union Local 424, 1993 (Box 8 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
- Labor/Management Files, 1981-2000; 2; 2.6 cubic ft.
  This series contains files related to Division 169's relationship with the Department of Environmental Conservation, the agency by which its members were employed. The heart of the series consists of minutes and agendas for labor/management meetings. These contractually-mandated meetings between PEF representatives and DEC managers took place several times each year. At these meetings, issues related to interpretation of the current PEF contract were discussed. Also included are files on DEC policies and operations, subject files on issues that were discussed at labor/management meetings, and files on DEC-specific PEF committees. The Health and Safety Committee files in this series relate to the PEF/ENCON - DEC Joint Statewide Health and Safety Committee, which should not be confused with the statewide PEF Health and Safety Committee. Files from statewide PEF's Health and Safety Committee are found in Series 4.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically.
  - Adjusted Work Schedule, 1983-1984; 1986; 1989 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 1)
  - Agency Work Force Management Plan, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 2)
  - Agent Orange, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 3)
  - Budget Reports, 1983-1986; 1990; 1994-1995; 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 4)
  - Captive Wildlife Policy, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 5)
  - Chairing Labor/Management Meetings, Workshop, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 6)
  - Civil Service, 1983-1986 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 7)
  - Civil Service, Jobs and Positions, 1983-1984; 1987-1990 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 8)
  - Clothing, Job-Related, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 9)
  - Commissioner Appointments, 1983; 1987 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 10)
  - Comprehensive Human Resources Development Procedures and Information Guide, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 11)
  - Conservationist Improper Practice Case, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 12)
  - Contract Grievances, 1986; 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1983-1984; 1988; 1990; 1992-1996; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 14)
  - "Dealing With Uncertainty and Change", DEC Report, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 15)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, 25th Anniversary Study, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 16)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, Affirmative Action Annual Report, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 17)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, Fiscal Bulletins, 1985-1988 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 18)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, News Clippings, 1991; 1996 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 19)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, Policies and Procedures Manual, Dissenting Professional Opinions, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 20)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation-related Proposed Legislation, 1983; 1995 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 21)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation and Union Organizational Charts, Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 22)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Visible Issues Reports, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 23)
  - Division of Air Resources, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 24)
  - Division of Fish and Wildlife, 1984-1985; 1996 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 25)
  - Education and Scholarship Program, 1992-1994; 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 26)
  - Employee Health Service, Section 72 Guidelines, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 27)
  - Employee Medical Monitoring Program, Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 28)
  - Engineering Technician Career Ladder, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 29)
  - Environmental Bond Act, 1986; 1990; 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 30)
  - Environmental Bond Act, Briefing, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 31)
  - Environmental Bond Act, Hiring Report, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 32)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 33)
  - Ethics Grievance, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 34)
  - Ethics Law, Amendments, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 35)
  - Fiscal Reimbursements, 1983-1985; 1987-1989; 1997-2000 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 36)
  - Foresters, 1983-1984; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 37)
  - Foresters, Regional Meeting, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 38)
  - Freedom of Information Law, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 39)
  - Hazardous Substances and Hazardous Duty, 1988; 1990; 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 40)
  - Health and Safety, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 41)
  - Health and Safety, DEC Organization and Delegation Memoranda, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 42)
  - Health and Safety, Task Force Agenda, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 43)
  - Health and Safety Committee, Minutes and Memoranda, 1981-1986; 1993-1999; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 44)
  - Health and Safety Issues, 1981-1982; 1984-1988; 1990-1994 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 45)
  - Health and Safety Issues, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 46)
  - Hiring Freeze Waivers, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 47)
  - Hydro-Mist Wastewater Treatment, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 48)
  - Inter-Office Policies and Procedures, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 49)
  - Job Vacancy Postings, 1989; 1993 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 50)
  - Labor/Management, Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 51)
  - Labor/Management, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 52)
  - Labor/Management, Correspondence, 1988-2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 53)
  - Labor/Management, Committee Training, 1989-1990; 1998-2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 54)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 55)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 56)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 57)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 1)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 2)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 3)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 4)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 5)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 6)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 7)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 8)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 9)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 10)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 11)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 12)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 13)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1994 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 14)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1995 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 15)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 16)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 17)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1998 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 18)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 19)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, Undated (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 20)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Minutes, Newsletter Form, 1985-1998 (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 21)
  - Labor/Management, Meeting Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 22)
  - Labor/Management, Meetings, Regional, 1982-1983; 1986 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 1)
  - Labor Relations Memos, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 2)
  - Layoffs/Leave Policies,1983-1984, 1986; 1992-1993; 1997 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 3)
  - Lobbying Letters, 1988; 1992; 1996; 1998 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 4)
  - Memoranda of Agreement, 1989-1990; 1996; 1997 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 5)
  - Minimum Exam Qualifications and Selection Requirements, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 6)
  - Negotiations, 1988; 1991; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 7)
  - New DEC Building, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 8)
  - New York State Performance Partnership Agreement, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 9)
  - Nursing Station Closures Lawsuit, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 10)
  - Occupational Accident, Injury, and Illness Data, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 11)
  - Ontario Public Service Employees Union, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 12)
  - Open Door Policy, 1989; 1994-1995 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 13)
  - Organization and Delegation Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 14)
  - Overtime Eligibility, 1984-1986; 1994 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 15)
  - Payroll, 1984-1986 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 16)
  - Performance Evaluation Program, 1982-1986; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 17)
  - Personnel Advisory Memoranda, 1998 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 18)
  - Pesticide Reallocations, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 19)
  - Policy, Miscellaneous, 1984; 1989; Undated (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 20)
  - Political Issues, Public Relations Materials, Undated (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 21)
  - Political Issues, Public Relations Materials, Non-PEF, 1984-1997 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 22)
  - Pollution and Energy Reduction Committee, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 23)
  - Position Papers, 1983-1990; 1992-1994; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 24)
  - Privacy and Public Records Laws, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 25)
  - Provisional Appointments, 1984-1997 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 26)
  - Quality of Worklife, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 27)
  - Quality through Participation, 1995-1997 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 28)
  - Regulatory Services, "Building Bridges" Campaign, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 29)
  - SEFA, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 30)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1987; 1992-1994 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 31)
  - Smoking Policy, 1984; 1986 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 32)
  - Technician Careers Committee, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 33)
  - Telecommuting, 1994; 1997; 1999 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 34)
  - Title Consolidation and Reallocation, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 35)
  - Vacancies/Hiring Correspondence, 1986; 1991; 1999; 2000 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 36)
  - Vehicle and Travel Policies, 1983-1984; 1986; 1990; 1992-1996; 1998-1999 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 37)
  - Voluntary Reduction in Work Schedule Program, 1984; 2000 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 38)
  - Woodlawn Beach Land Deal, 1990 (Box 3 (2-Labor/Management Files), Folder 39)
- Executive Board, 1978-2000; 3; 3.9 cubic ft.
  The bulk of this series consists of executive board meeting kits, which contain all material furnished to board members in advance of a scheduled meeting. This material usually includes a proposed agenda and minutes from the previous meeting for approval. Also included are correspondence and memos related to the meeting and to issues on the proposed agenda, as well as committee reports addressed to the president and executive board. Materials that were sometimes included are policy documents, financial documents and drafts of proposed annual budgets, and ethics grievance petitions. The Executive Board could choose to hear appeals of cases that had been previously decided by the Ethics Committee. A few folders contain handwritten notes taken at the meetings.
  Although the executive board meeting kits cover the period from 1979 through mid-2000, there are some gaps in coverage. Most significantly, there are no executive board kits for the period from July 1988 through July 1991. There is also no kit from the first quarter of 1997, and no kits for the period from June 1997 through November 1998.
  Also included in this series are executive board materials not associated with a particular meeting. Particularly notable are correspondence and news clippings detailing the founding of PEF, its struggle for legal recognition, and the formation of the original interim executive board during the period 1978-1979.
  - Executive Board, Conference Materials, 1979 March (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, Contract Meeting Kit, 1979 November 8 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, Contract Meeting Kit, 1985 June 6 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, Contract Meeting Kit, 1988 July 13 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, Contract Meeting Kit, 2000 June 27 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 5)
  - Executive Board, Correspondence, 1986-1992; 1999-2000 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 6)
  - Executive Board, Correspondence and News Clippings, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 7)
  - Executive Board, Ethics Committee Grievance Petitions and Reports, 1992 March-1992 November (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 8)
  - Executive Board, Mail Ballots, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 9)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Announcements and Agendas, 1983-1990 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 10)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Minutes, 1980-1982; 1993; 1995 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 11)
  - Executive Board, Meeting, Miscellaneous, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 12)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Reports by Board Members, 1984-1988; Undated (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 13)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Transcript Excerpts, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 14)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1978 October 26 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 15)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1978 October 26 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 16)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1979 January 24 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 17)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1979 April 4 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 18)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1979 August 29 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 19)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1980 February 20 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 20)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1980 May 16 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 21)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1980 August 12 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 22)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1980 October 12 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 23)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1980 November 5 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 24)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1980 December 11 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 25)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1981 February 8-1981 February 9 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 26)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1981 March 25 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 27)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1981 May 15 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 28)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1981 July 31 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 29)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1981 October 11 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 30)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1982 January 15 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 31)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1982 January 29 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 32)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1982 April 2 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 33)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1982 August 6-9; 1982 August 20 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 34)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1982 September 23 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 35)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1982 October 10 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 36)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1982 December 14 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 37)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1983 January 28 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 38)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1983 April 11 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 39)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1983 August 1-1983 August 3 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 40)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1983 August 1-1983 August 3 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 41)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1983 October 9 (Box 1 (3-Executive Board), Folder 42)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1984 January 26-1984 January 27 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1984 January 26-1984 January 27 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1984 March 13 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1984 May 11-1984 May 13 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1984 September 16-1984 September 18 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 5)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1984 November 27-1984 November 28 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 6)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1985 February 6-1985 February 8 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 7)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1985 April 30-1985 May 1 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 8)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1985 August 26-1985 August 27 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 9)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1985 October 30-1985 October 31 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 10)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1986 January 30-1986 January 31 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 11)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1986 March 3 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 12)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1986 May 7 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 13)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1986 June 26 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 14)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1986 August 25-1986 August 26 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 15)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, PAC Report, 1986 August 25-1986 August 26 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 16)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, Policy Manual, 1986 August 25-1986 August 26 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 17)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1987 January 28-1987 January 30 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 18)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1987 January 28-1987 January 30 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 19)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1987 April 23-1987 April 24 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 20)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1987 July 23-1987 July 24 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 21)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1987 November 5 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 22)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1987 December 1-1987 December 2 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 23)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1988 January 28-1988 January 29 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 24)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1988 May 12-1988 May 13 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 25)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1991 August 1-1991 August 2 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 26)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1991 August 1-1991 August 2 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 27)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Kit, 1991 November 6 (Box 2 (3-Executive Board), Folder 28)